Finding Aid for the Colonial Court Records Group, 1665-1787 SR.401
State Archives of North Carolina
- Civil and Criminal Action Papers, Supreme Courts, 1755-1759; SR.401.4; 401.4; CCR 139 - CCR 140; CCR 188; CCR 190 - CCR 192; CCR 198; Correspondence Receipts Accounts Dockets Lists; 1.800; General Court
  - Civil Action Papers, 1755-1759; SR.401.4.1; 1.600; General Court (Box Supreme Courts, Civil Action Papers, 1755-1756, Box Supreme Courts, Civil Action Papers, 1756-1757, Box Supreme Courts, Civil Action Papers, 1757-1758, Box Supreme Courts, Civil Action Papers, 1759)
    - Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 2, 1755; CCR 188; General Court (Folder Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 2)
    - Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 3, 1755; CCR 188; General Court (Folder Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 3)
    - Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 4, 1755; CCR 188; General Court (Folder Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 4)
    - Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 1, 1756; CCR 188; General Court (Folder Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 1)
    - Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 2, 1756; CCR 188; General Court (Folder Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 2)
    - Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 3, 1756; CCR 189; General Court (Folder Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 3)
    - Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 4, 1756; CCR 189; General Court (Folder Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 4)
    - Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 1, 1757; CCR 189; General Court (Folder Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 1)
    - Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 2, 1757; CCR 189; General Court (Folder Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 2)
    - Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 3, 1757; CCR 189; General Court (Folder Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 3)
    - Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 4, 1757; CCR 190; General Court (Folder Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 4)
    - Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 1, 1758; CCR 190; General Court (Folder Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 1)
    - Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 2, 1758; CCR 190; General Court (Folder Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 2)
    - Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 3, 1758; CCR 190; General Court (Folder Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 3)
    - Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 1, 1759; CCR 191; General Court (Folder Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 1)
    - Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 2, 1759; CCR 191; General Court (Folder Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 2)
    - Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 3, 1759; CCR 191; General Court (Folder Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 3)
    - Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 4, 1759; CCR 191; General Court (Folder Supreme Courts, Civil, folder 4)
  - Criminal Action Papers, 1755-1759; SR.401.4.2; 0.200; General Court (Box Supreme Courts, Criminal Action Papers, 1755-1759)
    This subseries is arranged chronologically by year and may contain documents belonging to the same case from different years.
    This subseries contains documents relating to criminal suits tried in the Supreme Courts of Justice within the five districts of Edenton, Edgecombe, New Bern, Salisbury, and Wilmington as well as the Courts of Oyer and Terminer and General Goal. Criminal Action Papers include cases involving assault, murder, robbery and theft, debt owed to the crown and treason against the crown and local government.
    - Supreme Courts, Criminal, 1755-1756; CCR 192; General Court (Folder Supreme Courts, Criminal)
    - Supreme Courts, Criminal, 1757; CCR 192; General Court (Folder Supreme Courts, Criminal)
    - Supreme Courts, Criminal, 1758; CCR 192; General Court (Folder Supreme Courts, Criminal)
    - Supreme Courts, Criminal, 1759; CCR 192; General Court (Folder Supreme Courts, Criminal)
- Civil and Criminal Action Papers, Other Courts, 1669-1775; SR.401.5; 401.5; CCR 142 - CCR 145; Minutes Interrogatories Writs Manifests; 0.200; Colonial Courts; Vice Admirality Court (Box Other Courts, 1669-1775)
  This series is arranged by type of court.
  This series consists of documents from the other various courts of colonial North Carolina. Included are the Palatine Court, Court of Chancery and the Vice Admiralty Court. Materials include bills in Chancery (complaints), bonds, depositions, petitions, summons and arrest warrants, examinations, narratives and judges' fees for the Vice Admiralty Court. Also included are documents from the General Court that pertain to cases being tried in the other courts.
  - Palatine Court, 1669-1729; CCR 193; Colonial Courts (Folder Palatine Court)
  - Court of Chancery, 1689-1775; CCR 193; Colonial Courts (Folder Court of Chancery)
  - Court of Chancery, 1770; CCR 193; Colonial Courts (Folder Court of Chancery)
  - Vice Admiralty Court, 1720-1729; CCR 193; Colonial Courts (Folder Vice Admiralty Court)
  - Vice Admiralty Court, 1730-1739; CCR 193; Colonial Courts (Folder Vice Admiralty Court)
  - Vice Admiralty Court, 1740-1749; CCR 193; Colonial Courts (Folder Vice Admiralty Court)
  - Vice Admiralty Court, 1750-7159; CCR 193; Colonial Courts (Folder Vice Admiralty Court)
  - Vice Admiralty Court, 1770; CCR 193; Colonial Courts (Folder Vice Admiralty Court)
  - Vice Admiralty Court, n.d., [1720-1770]; CCR 193; Colonial Courts (Folder Vice Admiralty Court, n.d.)
- Subject Files, 1680-1769; SR.401.6; 401.6; CCR 141; Indictments Warrants Bonds (legal records); 0.400; Colonial Courts; Edenton District Superior Court; Court of Oyer and Terminer and General Gaol Delivery (Box Subject Files)
  This series is arranged alphabetically by subject.
  This series contains various documents pertaining to specific subjects associated with the courts. Themes include cases relating to maritime, slavery, servants and apprenticeships, Native Americans, infrastructure, business and trade, marriage, and bills of sale for chattels. Materials include petitions for the construction of ferries, road and building repair, shipwrecks, shipping bonds, pardons, indictments, treaties, court cases, agreements, and petitions.
  - Maritime: Ships, Shipping, and Wrecks, 1677-1762; CCR 194; Colonial Courts (Folder Maritime: Ships, Shipping, and Wrecks)
  - Maritime: Vessel Bonds, 1759; CCR 194; Colonial Courts (Folder Maritime: Vessel Bonds)
  - Infrastructure: Public Buildings, 1737; CCR 194; Colonial Courts (Folder Infrastructure: Public Buildings)
  - Infrastructure: Ferries, 1722-1742; CCR 194; Colonial Courts (Folder Infrastructure: Ferries)
  - Infrastructure: Roads, 1694-1725; CCR 194; Colonial Courts (Folder Infrastructure: Roads)
  - Infrastructure: Road Repair (Criminal), 1735-1736; CCR 194; Colonial Courts (Folder Infrastructure: Road Repair (Criminal))
  - Infrastructure: Repair of King's Highway (Criminal), 1739-1742; CCR 194; Colonial Courts (Folder Infrastructure: Repair of King's Highway (Criminal))
  - Business and Trade: New Pennyslvania Company Litigations, 1699-1713; CCR 194; Colonial Courts (Folder Business and Trade: New Pennyslvania Company Litigations)
  - Business and Trade: Ordinaries, 1694, 1727; CCR 194; Colonial Courts (Folder Business and Trade: Ordinaries)
  - Business and Trade: Accounts and Duties, 1695-1739; CCR 194; Colonial Courts (Folder Business and Trade: Accounts and Duties)
  - Marriages, 1686-1736; CCR 194; Colonial Courts (Folder Marriages)
  - Concerning Native Americans (Indians), 1697-1769; CCR 194; Colonial Courts (Folder Concerning Native Americans (Indians))
  - Slavery: Runaways, Sale and Trade, Ownership, etc., 1698-1746; CCR 194; Colonial Courts (Folder Slavery: Runaways, Sale and Trade, Ownership, etc.)
  - Slavery: Freedom of Slaves, 1714-1717; CCR 194; Colonial Courts (Folder Slavery: Freedom of Slaves)
  - Slavery: Crimes, 1715-1732; CCR 194; Colonial Courts (Folder Slavery: Crimes)
  - Indentured Servants, 1699-1729; CCR 194; Colonial Courts (Folder Indentured Servants)
  - Apprentice Papers, 1695-1736; CCR 194; Colonial Courts (Folder Apprentice Papers)
  - Bills of Sale for Chattels, 1686-1736; CCR 194; Colonial Courts (Folder Bills of Sale for Chattels)
- Miscellaneous Court Records, 1677-1764; SR.401.7; 401.7; C.C.R.187; Wills Land grants Deeds Petitions Inventories Recommendations; 0.200; Colonial Courts (Box Miscellaneous Court Records, 1677-1764, n.d.)
  This series contains court documents that fall under the administrative side of the court and other miscellaneous court activities and proceedings. Materials include pardons, licensing, appointments, commissions, bills of exchange, Inquests, law, and documents regarding the House of Burgess.
  - Appointments, Power of Attorney/ Warrant of Attorney, 1677-1743; CCR 195; Colonial Courts (Folder Appointments, Power of Attorney/ Warrant of Attorney)
  - Appointments, Commissions, Petition for Commission, 1689-1725; CCR 195; Colonial Courts (Folder Appointments, Commissions, Petition for Commission)
  - Bills of Exchange, 1708, 1731; CCR 195; Colonial Courts (Folder Bills of Exchange)
  - Commissions of Oyer and Terminer for Edenton, 1754; CCR 195; Colonial Courts (Folder Commissions of Oyer and Terminer for Edenton)
  - House of Burgess, Gov. and Council, Acts, Proclamations, Petitions and Instructions, 1679-1742; CCR 195; Colonial Courts (Folder House of Burgess, Gov. and Council, Acts, Proclamations, Petitions and Instructions)
  - Inquests, 1690-1745; CCR 195; Colonial Courts (Folder Inquests)
  - Instructions of Lord Granville to Agents of N.C., 1744, 1756; CCR 195; Colonial Courts (Folder Instructions of Lord Granville to Agents of N.C.)
  - Law, 1703, 1748; CCR 195; Colonial Courts (Folder Law)
  - Licenses, 1725, 1740; CCR 195; Colonial Courts (Folder Licenses)
  - Micellaneous and Pieces, CCR 195; Colonial Courts (Folder Micellaneous and Pieces)
  - Oaths and Pledges, CCR 195; Colonial Courts (Folder Oaths and Pledges)
  - Pardon, John Tucler from Virginia, 1736; CCR 195; Colonial Courts (Folder Pardon, John Tucler from Virginia)
  - Petition for Citizenship, 1690; CCR 195; Colonial Courts (Folder Petition for Citizenship)
  - Recognizances, List of General Sessions, 1737; CCR 195; Colonial Courts (Folder Recognizances, List of General Sessions)
- Estate Papers, 1665-1767; SR.401.8; 5.000; Colonial Courts (Box Estate Papers, Adams-Branston, 1665-1767, Box Estate Papers, Brasely-Child, 1665-1767, Box Estate Papers, Church-Eaves, 1665-1767, Box Estate Papers, Edgerton-Haughton, 1665-1767, Box Estate Papers, Hawkins-Hyde, 1665-1767, Box Estate Papers, Ingram-Lowry, 1665-1767, Box Estate Papers, MacCray-Moore, 1665-1767, Box Estate Papers, Morgan-Pointavinte, 1665-1767, Box Estate Papers, Pollock-Rigney, 1665-1767, Box Estate Papers, Roberts-Slocum, 1665-1767, Box Estate Papers, Small-Travis, 1665-1767, Box Estate Papers, Trotter-Wilson, 1665-1767, Box Estate Papers, Winsley-Young; Misc., 1665-1767)
  This series is arranged alphabetically by last name. Dates refer to the date range as seen on the documents in each file.
  This series contains documents relating to individuals' estates. Materials include cases of debt settlements, writs, bonds, depositions, petitions, pleas, probates, appointments of executors, lawyer and office fees, narratives, attachments, declarations, agreements, and summons.
  - Adams, Abraham, 1736; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Adams, Abraham)
  - Adams, Peter, 1745-1755; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Adams, Peter)
  - Adderly, John, 1741-1742; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Adderly, John)
  - Akehurst, Daniel, 1700-1713; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Akehurst, Daniel)
  - Albory, Emanuell, n.d.; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Albory, Emanuell)
  - Alleyn, Dr, George, 1734-1737; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Alleyn, Dr, George)
  - Allein, Richard, 1740-1745; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Allein, Richard)
  - Allgrow, Nicholas, n.d.; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Allgrow, Nicholas)
  - Allison, John, 1738-1746; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Allison, John)
  - Anderson, Joseph, 1743-1758; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Anderson, Joseph)
  - Ardrene, John, n.d.; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Ardrene, John)
  - Armstrong, Thomas, 1735-1741; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Armstrong, Thomas)
  - Ashburn, William, 1740-1745; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Ashburn, William)
  - Ashe, John Baptist, 1741-1745; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Ashe, John Baptist)
  - Atkins, Robert, 1729-1736; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Atkins, Robert)
  - Atkinson, Benjamin, 1735-1737; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Atkinson, Benjamin)
  - Attaway, Thomas, n.d.; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Attaway, Thomas)
  - Aveline, Petter, 1714-1715; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Aveline, Petter)
  - Badham, William, 1738; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Badham, William)
  - Baker, Henry, 1739-1745; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Baker, Henry)
  - Baker, Nathan, 1728-1745; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Baker, Nathan)
  - Barber, Charles, 1739-1740; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Barber, Charles)
  - Barefield, Richard, 1729; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Barefield, Richard)
  - Bartlett, William, 1698; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Bartlett, William)
  - Bateman, Jonathan, 1696; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Bateman, Jonathan)
  - Battle, John, 1694; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Battle, John)
  - Beard, James, n.d.; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Beard, James)
  - Becket, Christopher, 1736-1741; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Becket, Christopher)
  - Bell, Thomas, 1734-1735; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Bell, Thomas)
  - Bell, william, Sr., 1724-1734; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Bell, william, Sr.)
  - Benbury, William, 1755-1756; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Benbury, William)
  - Bennett, Edward, n.d.; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Bennett, Edward)
  - Bentley, John, n.d.; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Bentley, John)
  - Betterly, Thomas, 1729-1733; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Betterly, Thomas)
  - Biggs, Timothy, 1687; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Biggs, Timothy)
  - Birkenhead, George, 1723; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Birkenhead, George)
  - Blackburn, Oliver, 1732-1743; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Blackburn, Oliver)
  - Blainy, George, n.d.; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Blainy, George)
  - Blanchard, Robert, 1742; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Blanchard, Robert)
  - Blanshard, Ephraim, 1740-1757; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Blanshard, Ephraim)
  - Blish (Blysh), John, 1719-1721; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Blish (Blysh), John)
  - Blount, James, n.d.; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Blount, James)
  - Blount, Thomas, 1706-1727; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Blount, Thomas)
  - Bolton, Humfrey, 1700; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Bolton, Humfrey)
  - Bolton, John, n.d.; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Bolton, John)
  - Bond, Richard, 1727-1728; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Bond, Richard)
  - Boon, James, 1736-1739; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Boon, James)
  - Bornitt, John, 1704; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Bornitt, John)
  - Bouchier, Thomas, 1703-1704; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Bouchier, Thomas)
  - Bould, George, 1746; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Bould, George)
  - Boush, Maximillian, 1729; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Boush, Maximillian)
  - Bowman, James, 1716-1736; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Bowman, James)
  - Boyd, John, 1742; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Boyd, John)
  - Boyd, John, Rev., 1739-1756; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Boyd, John, Rev.)
  - Boyd, Thomas, 1725-1727; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Boyd, Thomas)
  - Body, Thomas (Col.), 1714-1732; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Body, Thomas (Col.))
  - Boyde, John, 1726; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Boyde, John)
  - Branch, Ann, 1741; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Branch, Ann)
  - Branch, William, 1717-1726; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Branch, William)
  - Branston, Robert, 1669-1724; CCR 196; Colonial Courts (Folder Branston, Robert)
  - Brasely, Frances, 1741; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Brasely, Frances)
  - Braswell, William, 1723-1724; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Braswell, William)
  - Bray, William (Cpt.), 1715; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Bray, William (Cpt.))
  - Brent, Stephen, 1736-1756; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Brent, Stephen)
  - Brim, William, 1717-1723; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Brim, William)
  - Brothers, John, 1740-1742; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Brothers, John)
  - Brothers, Thomas, 1741; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Brothers, Thomas)
  - Brothers, William, 1712; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Brothers, William)
  - Brounson, Isaac, 1718-1724; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Brounson, Isaac)
  - Brown, John, 1744; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Brown, John)
  - Brown, Robert, 1732; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Brown, Robert)
  - Bryer, John, 1755; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Bryer, John)
  - Buckbird, Henry, 1731-1733; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Buckbird, Henry)
  - Bunch, Paul, 1741; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Bunch, Paul)
  - Bundy, Caleb, Jr., 1722-1723; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Bundy, Caleb, Jr.)
  - Burnett, Archibald, 1745; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Burnett, Archibald)
  - Bustion, Christopher, 1722-1732; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Bustion, Christopher)
  - Butler, Christopher, 1703-1704; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Butler, Christopher)
  - Butler, John, 1699; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Butler, John)
  - Buxton, Edward, 1741-1745; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Buxton, Edward)
  - Calfe, Robert, 1707-1725; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Calfe, Robert)
  - Calvert, Dorothy, 1740-1742; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Calvert, Dorothy)
  - Campain, Robert, 1723-1746; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Campain, Robert)
  - Campbell, Eloazor A., 1739; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Campbell, Eloazor A.)
  - Campbell, Hugh, 1737-1741; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Campbell, Hugh)
  - Cann, John, 1718-1724; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Cann, John)
  - Cannon, John, n.d.; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Cannon, John)
  - Cannon, Robert, 1755; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Cannon, Robert)
  - Caron, Jacob, 1754-1756; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Caron, Jacob)
  - Caron, John, 1758-1761; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Caron, John)
  - Carroll, Charles, 1724; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Carroll, Charles)
  - Caruthers, Thomas, Dr., 1724-1751; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Caruthers, Thomas, Dr.)
  - Carver, James, 1742; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Carver, James)
  - Cary, Thomas, 1722; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Cary, Thomas)
  - Casno, Isaac (minor), 1739-1740; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Casno, Isaac (minor))
  - Catchmaid, Edward (see also Ketchmaid), 1701-1721; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Catchmaid, Edward (see also Ketchmaid))
  - Catchmaid, George (see also Ketchmaid), n.d.; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Catchmaid, George (see also Ketchmaid))
  - Chamard, George, 1737-1739; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Chamard, George)
  - Chambers, George, n.d.; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Chambers, George)
  - Chandler, Benjamin, 1739; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Chandler, Benjamin)
  - Chapman, Benjamin, 1711-1722; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Chapman, Benjamin)
  - Chapman, John, 1738-1739; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Chapman, John)
  - Cherryholm, John, 1729; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Cherryholm, John)
  - Chester, Joseph, 1746; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Chester, Joseph)
  - Chever, Samuel, 1740-1741; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Chever, Samuel)
  - Child, Thomas, 1755; CCR 197; Colonial Courts (Folder Child, Thomas)
  - Church, Elizabeth, 1759-1761; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Church, Elizabeth)
  - Eaves, Ralph, 1741-1744; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Eaves, Ralph)
  - Church, Richard, 1759; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Church, Richard)
  - Clapham, Joseph, 1729-1739; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Clapham, Joseph)
  - Clapham, Josiah, 1736; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Clapham, Josiah)
  - Clarke, Thomas, 1718-1722; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Clarke, Thomas)
  - Clayton, Henry, 1726-1730; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Clayton, Henry)
  - Clayton, Zebulon, 1737; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Clayton, Zebulon)
  - Cleeves, Emanual, 1717; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Cleeves, Emanual)
  - Clements, George, 1723-1731; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Clements, George)
  - Colbert, Dorothy, 1741; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Colbert, Dorothy)
  - Cole, James, Major, 1715-1718; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Cole, James, Major)
  - Colles, Thomas, 1721; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Colles, Thomas)
  - Collins, Alice, 1707-1712; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Collins, Alice)
  - Collins, Richard, n.d.; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Collins, Richard)
  - Collins, William, 1709; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Collins, William)
  - Comander, Joseph, 1693-1707; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Comander, Joseph)
  - Compain, Robert, 1745; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Compain, Robert)
  - Conner, John, 1740-1743; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Conner, John)
  - Cook, William, 1745; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Cook, William)
  - Corkey, Patrick, 1742-1743; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Corkey, Patrick)
  - Cortes, George, 1741; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Cortes, George)
  - Cotton, John, 1720-1728; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Cotton, John)
  - Council, John, 1741-1745; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Council, John)
  - Craghilll, Thomas, 1721-1733; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Craghilll, Thomas)
  - Craige, Richard, n.d.; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Craige, Richard)
  - Craven, James, 1755-1756; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Craven, James)
  - Crawley, William, 1734-1739; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Crawley, William)
  - Crisp, John, 1731-1732; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Crisp, John)
  - Crispe, Nicholas, 1729-1731; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Crispe, Nicholas)
  - Cruise, Lawrence, n.d.; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Cruise, Lawrence)
  - Culle, John, 1691-1720; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Culle, John)
  - Culpeper, John, 1678-1696; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Culpeper, John)
  - Curlee, John, 1718; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Curlee, John)
  - Curtis, Silvanus, 1744; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Curtis, Silvanus)
  - Cutlett, Thomas, 1704; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Cutlett, Thomas)
  - Daniel, William, 1735-1745; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Daniel, William)
  - Daniell, Owing, 1702; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Daniell, Owing)
  - Dann, John, 1686; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Dann, John)
  - Darnell, Thomas (minor), n.d.; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Darnell, Thomas (minor))
  - Daugherty, John, 1697; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Daugherty, John)
  - Davis, Arthur, 1734-1739; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Davis, Arthur)
  - Davis, John (minor), 1693; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Davis, John (minor))
  - Davis, Peter, 1724; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Davis, Peter)
  - Davis, Samuel, 1756; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Davis, Samuel)
  - Davis, Thomas, 1755-1756; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Davis, Thomas)
  - Dawkins, William, 1714; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Dawkins, William)
  - Dawson, William, 1746; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Dawson, William)
  - Dear, John, n.d.; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Dear, John)
  - Deare, George, 1700; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Deare, George)
  - [Donige?], Geo, n.d.; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder [Donige?], Geo)
  - Downing, William, 1748-1758; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Downing, William)
  - Dry, William, 1737-1742; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Dry, William)
  - Duckinfield, William, 1739; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Duckinfield, William)
  - Dunpun, Martha, 1749; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Dunpun, Martha)
  - Dunston, Eleanor (ward), 1741-1748; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Dunston, Eleanor (ward))